To be continued...
...demons, devils, and bloodsuckers.
Let's see, where to begin?
Don't. You can spare us the lecture, Shinoa.
Let's do this.
Hold it.
You're gonna try it at the same time?
What if something goes wrong?
Your demon could get out of control.
You remember when Yoichi tried to kill us?
That's why we came out here, so you can't hurt anything.
Out of control?
Huh? What did you say?
Nothing.
Hey, guys!
What is it?
It's the four horsemen of John.
Three of them.
No, make that five.
Crap. We need to deal with them.
All right. Let's get this over with fast.
Destroy our enemies, Gekkoine.
Let's protect everyone.
You guys, I did it.
Did you just manifest your demons? Since when can you do that?
Explain how that's possible, Shinoa.
Have you been giving him private lessons or something?
No. Yoichi's mastered manifestation on his own.
He's always had exceptional curse control abilities.
He's got a surprisingly strong relationship with his demon.
Seriously?
Yeah. I've been talking to my demon before I go to sleep and in my dreams.
Now I just sort of get how to do it.
Okay, Ashuromaru. Drink my blood.
You wait!
Prepare to fight!
Is he okay?
What just happened to him?
I'm not sure.
He didn't immediately go berserk, so that's a big improvement.
Right now, he's more than likely trying to make contact with his demon.
We'll have to stand watch over him until he regains full consciousness.
Don't look so worried.
We're here to look out for our family, aren't we, boy?
You
Trouble as usual. What do you mean? It's not you's fault
Just saying
Yoichi and I were interrogated and tortured by the Hiragis the whole reason is because they wanted to know more about what he did
Yeah, and what did you tell them about it?
Exactly what you ordered us to but I didn't know what they were talking about
You did the right thing and you still think it's smart that we don't tell you he completely lost control
Because it kind of looks like you're trying to manipulate him for some reason, but you wouldn't do that to your teammate, right?
What if I did I don't know? I'd still follow orders to keep my sister safe
I'd have to swallow down vomit every time I saw you. Hey, you can't talk to your superior like that
She know what is just trying to protect you from the people in the upper
It's okay, Mitsu
And what about you, Yoichi? What do you think?
Oh
well, I
I
Get why you don't want to tell you about what happened when he lost control because that might cause him to freak out, but
You want a better explanation, don't you?
Hmm
We're comrades, aren't we? So tell us your reasoning
You're right about that. We should trust each other. Keeping secrets could drive us apart
All right, then
Let's talk about all of this when you's awake and the training's over
Not just about what happened to him, but about where we stand as a unit, too
Can I get all your help here, you guys?
Hold him!
Looks like it's starting
Yeah, I think he's finally found his doom
He never should have been born
We must kill the Seraph of the End
He's the devil's child, not our son
The boy is a monster
Dad, what's wrong?
You, don't fight it
Come here
I'm gonna send you to a better place, son
You should have died here with the others
Everyone else is dead because you ran away like a coward
Fall apart, you
If you think this memory will make me lose control, Ashura Maru
Then you've underestimated me
And how much there is at stake
I made him a promise and I intend to keep it
Come on, you
Let's protect our family together
Please, I'm counting on you
I know
I couldn't save you if you didn't want my help
I won't fall for any of your demonic tricks
Oh man, I thought I had you there for a second
I know how you fight and this time I was prepared
No need to act so tough
After all, I know all of your secrets
Try to tear me down all you want
But if Mika, Gurin or Shinoa and the others need my help
I'll do whatever it takes to keep them safe
Oh yeah? You're stronger than the last time we talked
To be honest, this new devil-may-care attitude of yours is sort of annoying
What are you gonna do about it?
I'm gonna kill you
What the hell are you doing?
I didn't come here because I want to hurt you
Then what do you want?
I need you, Ashuromaru
Your strength
Will you help me save Mika?
I suppose I could, but what's in it for me if I do?
If you help me, then I'll be your friend
It's tough being alone
And difficult to feel like you're unwanted or that you've been abandoned
I know what that's like
And you think being my friend will change all of that?
Yeah
He's awake!
Hey
I hope I didn't cause you guys to worry or anything
You're back
I mean, it's really you, right?
Jeez, you look like you were gonna die on us there for a minute
Oh, sorry, I didn't know what was going on with my body
So, were you actually successful?
And I guess it was worth it
Am I the only one who's exhausted from all this?
Let's just wait to do Komizuki's training later
Huh? No way, we're doing it right now
It's getting late and honestly, I'm kinda hungry
No one cares if you're hungry
Well, it took you long enough
So, how was it? Are you okay?
I guess you were able to fight off the psychological attacks
Yeah, but I knew I wasn't alone
Not now that I have you guys
Huh?
Never mind
It's nothing
Well, to put it simply
The humans are being blinded by their desire to defeat us
And are partaking in forbidden experimentation they don't fully understand
It's quite unsettling
If you'll just watch this recording, you'll understand exactly what I mean
What was that thing?
This could be disastrous for us
There, you see? The humans have finally succeeded
They have managed to weaponize the Seraph of the End
I don't have to tell you what a serious problem this is
But Queen Cruel put an end to the humans' experiments when she exterminated the Hyakuya sect
That's right
This program was dismantled eight years ago
I killed the researchers and every child carrying even a trace of the Seraph of the End with my own hands
Oh-ho! You're sure you killed all the test subjects?
That's what I said, isn't it?
But if that's true, then how has the research come so far?
There were no organizations anywhere close to this sort of success other than the Hyakuya sect
Cool, I'm afraid that if your leadership failed, this could end up a major liability for the other
Hold your tongue less, Carr, or I'll have it ripped out and hung on my wall!
Oh, have I touched a nerve? Perhaps this is too much for you
Maybe it's time I stepped in as the new ruler of Japan
Don't push me, little brat
You're only 200 years older than me, Cruel
Besides, we both know that I'm stronger
Oh, come now!
Please don't argue!
Let's remember why we're here
How do we respond to the humans' successful weaponization?
What would you ask us to do, Queen Cruel?
This doesn't change our basic strategy
We'll send our strongest units in to destroy the demon army!
Looking forward to your success
By the way, Ferret Bathory
Who is the young boy standing behind you?
What the hell do you think you're doing?!
How dare you spring that video on me!
And bringing Mikayla along as well!
Conspire against me and I'll end you!
So scary!
But you forget that you can't kill me
After all, if I died
Think about what might happen
All the information I've collected on you
Could leak to the Progenitor Council
Besides, if they found out I let you escape
I'd be punished too
Dear, with all these shared secrets
It would appear that you and I have no other choice
But to be allies
Hooray!
You might even say
We belong together
Ah, who am I kidding?
What a fun game this is turning out to be!
Cruel
Kameizuki! You have to bite it!
Talk to me, Shinoa!
Was I just messed up?!
No, we might be in for a little trouble with him
trouble with him. I think the demon might be trying to take over his body. What? What are we
supposed to do if it does? You! I need you to be ready to attack just in case.
Die! He's so desperate. I'll make you yield to me, Kisekiyo.
If that's the goal, you're gonna have to try harder.
Poor little weakling. Your body is all mine.
Now to break you.
Big brother.
Don't worry.
So, how's Mirai doing?
Not good. I think she's getting worse.
Look, we've got a problem. Food's running out. We won't last three days with what we've got.
What are we gonna do?
Leave. Tomorrow morning at the crack of dawn.
Can't we wait longer? I'll have to figure out how to move Mirai.
You have to leave her behind. She'd just slow us down.
Are you out of your mind?
Hey, calm down. We have to be logical. Your sister is way beyond our help. It sucks, but
we've got to look out for the little ones who've survived, not to mention our own lives. It's
a crappy world, Kimizuki. And we can't save everyone. You take care of her. It's what's best for all of us.
You monster. How could you?
Mirai's the one who came up with the idea. She said she doesn't want to get in your way,
but she can't take her own life because she's too weak. Come on.
If you can't man up and follow through with this, then I'll do it myself.
Hold on!
Wait! Kimizuki!
Open the door! Let us in!
Crap! This way! We'll climb over the balcony!
Why do you have a knife?
Dammit!
Hey, big brother. I don't want to see you wasting away just because I'm too sick to get out of bed.
Shut up, Mirai.
Brother, please kill me.
Do it now and it'll all be over before you know it. You'll be free to live your life however you want.
Shut up! Just shut up! How can you say things like that?
I can hear your thoughts. Just now you were wondering what it'd be like to be rid of me.
I'm sick of taking care of her. She's holding me back. I'm just a kid too. I shouldn't have to do this.
If I could just kill my sister right here.
I didn't.
Wouldn't it be easier if I ran away from this burden and never left back?
That's what you just thought, big brother.
Shut up!
I'm not wrong, Shiho Kamizuki. Follow your instincts and free yourself.
Thank you, big brother, for finally putting me out of my misery.
I'm so sorry, Mirai.
You don't need to apologize. This was all my idea, remember? It's what I wanted.
Before I do this, can I ask you something?
I recently met this really stupid guy who I absolutely hate.
Now I can't seem to get away from him even though he might be the most annoying person on the planet.
Anyway, he says he'll risk his life to protect the people he cares about.
Even if his family isn't related to him by blood. That's crazy, right? I mean, the guy's a moron.
Indeed.
I know. And it's driving me crazy that he might be a better person than me.
He'd give up so much for people he's not related to. So how could I possibly kill my own sister?
I'd rather...
No, don't! What are you...
It's over now.
Well, I'll be damned.
Come, Kisekio.
He's possessed!
Whoa, relax, everyone. There's nothing to worry about.
It really is him.
Hey!
If that's true, then how come you attacked me?
Because we need to settle this once and for all and see who's stronger, you or me.
You outsmarted your demon.
Yep, and now I can use possession to beat your ass at any time.
Oh, yes? You want to do this for real?
Wait, what are you morons doing? Stop my...
All right, this could be very interesting.
Come.
Ashura Mori!
Fan out! Ashura Kanan!
Try not to cry, Kimizuki.
Nice try, but on the count of nine, I'm opening the devil's coffin.
Kisekio!
One, two, three, four.
Hey! Don't you run away from this fight!
I'm not gonna stand by and get killed by some murder coffin!
That thing looks super scary, man!
He may be dumb, but he's got good instincts.
What?
Still, it was my hatred for him that helped me overcome my demon.
I was just saying that you're a real pain in my ass!
Oh, screw you! If you think I'm bad, wait till you get a taste of my sword!
Come on, guys! Can't we all just get along?
Well, I guess that was interesting.
Yes.
It's curious.
They both tried to use special abilities that should be way above their skill levels.
And Yoichi was able to conjure a manifestation without any real training.
Where did Lieutenant Colonel Gurren find these guys, anyway?
Wait, that can't be right!
There's nothing. Their records start when they join the army.
All the data on their past has been deleted.
Who would do that?
It had to have been the Lieutenant Colonel.
You think Gurren is trying to hide his team's history from the higher-ranking officers?
Possibly, but I wouldn't be surprised if there was more to it than that.
Like what?
Human experimentation.
And war with the vampires.
I've got a feeling that something horrible is about to happen,
and that we're totally unprepared for it.
has been.
I'm just curious.
You know what?
You talked about helping people to use the
Next time on Seraph of the End, Ambition in the Demon Army.